Finding Aid for the J. Paul Getty Trust Inventory of Getty Publications, 1954-2013 and undated IA10020
Institutional Records and Archives
- Getty Conservation Institute (GCI), 1974-1998; 2000,; 2002,; 2006,; 2008-2013; Series II.
  - Rainer, Leslie and Angelyn Bass River, eds.The Conservation of Decorated Surfaces on Earthen Architecture. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-01)
  - Schweidler, Max. The Restoration of Engravings, Drawings, Books, and Other Works on Paper. Translated by Roy Perkinson. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-01)
  - Letellier, Robin. Recording, Documentation, and Information Management for the Conservation of Heritage Places: Guiding Principles. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
  - Bassett, Jane. The Craftsman Revealed: Adriaen de Vries, Sculptor in Bronze. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-03)
  - Ben Abed, Aїcha, Martha Demas, Thomas Roby, eds. Lessons Learned: Reflecting on the Theory and Practice of Mosaic Conservation. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-02)
  - Caneva, Giulia, Maria Pia Nugari, and Ornella Salvadori, eds.Plant Biology for Cultural Heritage: Biodeterioration and Conservation. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-02)
  - Howe, Kathryn Welch. The Los Angeles Historic Resource Survey Report: A Framework for a Citywide Historic Resource Survey. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2010.IA.01-01)
  - Learner, Thomas J. S., Patricia Smithen, Jay W. Krueger, and Michael R. Schilling, eds. Modern Paints Uncovered: Proceedings from the Modern Paints Uncovered Symposium: Organized by the Getty Conservation Institute, Tate, and the National Gallery of Art: Tate Modern, London, May 16-19, 2006. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-02)
  - Jurgens, Martin C. The Digital Print: Identification and Preservation. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-03)
  - Kimbo, Edna E, Julia G. Costello, and Tevvy Ball. The California Missions: History, Art and Preservation. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-03)
  - Lavedrine, Bertrand. Photographs of the Past: Process and Preservation. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-03)
  - Agnew, Neville, ed. Conservation of Ancient Sites on the Silk Road: Proceedings of the Second International Conference on the Conservation of Grotto Sites, Mogao Grottoes, Dunhuang, People's Republic of China, June 28-July 3, 2004. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-01)
  - Considine, Brian, Julie Wolfe, Katrina Posner, and Michel Bouchard. Conserving Outdoor Sculpture: the Stark Collection at the Getty Center. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-01)
  - Doehne, Eric and Clifford A. Price. Stone Conservation: An Overview of Current Research, Second Edition. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-03)
  - Lake, Susan F. Willem De Kooning: The Artist's Materials. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-03)
  - Hess Norris, Debra and Jennifer Jae Gutierrez, eds. Issues in the Conservation of Photographs. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-01)
  - Brooks, Mary M., and Dinah D. Eastop, eds.Changing Views of Textile Conservation. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-03)
  - Rainer, Leslie, Angelyn Bass Rivera and David Gandreau, eds.Terra 2008: The 10th International Conference of the Study and Conservation of Earthen Architectural Heritage. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-03)
  - Standeven, Harriet A. L. House Paints, 1900-1960: History and Use. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-03)
  - Chiantore, Oscar, and Antonio Rava. Conserving Contemporary Art: Issues, Methods, Materials, and Research. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2013.IA.01-2)
  - Gottschaller, Pia. Lucio Fontana: The Artist's Materials. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2012.IA.01-30)
  - Sullivan, Sharon, and Richard Mackay, eds. Archaeological Sites: Conservation and Management. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2013.IA.01-2)
  - Ferraini, Barbara, and Marina Pugliese, eds. Ephemeral Monuments: History and Conservation of Installation Art. Los Angeles: 20123. (Box 2013.IA.01-3)
  - Staniforth, Sarah, ed. Historical Perspectives on Preventive Conservation. Los Angeles: 2013. (Box 2013.IA.01-3)
- Getty Center for the History of Art and the Humanities (GCHAH) and Getty Research Institute (GRI), 1985-1991; 1994-2013,; undated; Series III.
  Material comprises Getty publications produced by or about the activities of the Getty Research Institute and its predecessor, the Getty Center for the History of Art and the Humanities.
  The Getty Research Institute (GRI) is dedicated to the study of the visual arts, approaching the topic from broad historical and cultural perspectives. The GRI's goals are to promote innovative scholarship in the arts and humanities, to bridge traditional academic boundaries, and to provide a unique environment for research, critical inquiry, and debate. The GRI is an operating program of the J. Paul Getty Trust, an international cultural and philanthropic organization serving both general audiences and specialized professionals. The Trust is a not-for-profit institution, educational in purpose and character, that focuses on the visual arts in all of their dimensions.
  The Getty Research Institute grew out of the Getty Center for the History of Art and the Humanities (GCHAH), which was established to advance and disseminate research in the history of art and the humanities. The GCHAH was one of the original programs established by the J. Paul Getty Trust. In 1981 the Trust began a year of exploration to determine where it would focus its resources and energies in order to make the greatest possible contribution to the field of art and art history as a whole. In 1982, following extensive international deliberations with knowledgeable individuals, the trustees made commitments to three new entities, a Conservation Institute, a Center for Education in the Arts, and a Center for the History of Art and the Humanities (GCHAH).
  From its inception the objective of the GCHAH was to foster advanced research in art, its history, diversity, and meaning in our culture and to do so by engaging scholars from various disciplines in the humanities. The proposed center was to include a residence program for scholars, a major expansion of the library, a modest publications program, and an art photo archive. The activities of the center were also to focus on preserving historic materials in the field of art history and the development of new reference tools for the field, using the latest in information technologies. The plan was approved, and in July 1983 the program known as the Getty Center for the History of Art and the Humanities opened in Santa Monica, California.
  Due to expanded operations and limited space at the original J. Paul Getty Museum near Malibu, California the various programs of the J. Paul Getty Trust were located at different sites throughout the Los Angeles basin during the 1980s and early 1990s. The Trust's vision was to bring together most of their programs at a single site. Meanwhile, the Getty Center in nearby Brentwood was under construction. In 1996, in order to avoid confusion with the soon-to-open Getty Center in Brentwood, the GCHAH was renamed the Getty Research Institute for the History of Art and the Humanities. The Getty Research Institute for the History of Art and the Humanities moved to the Getty Center in I997. In 2000 the program's name was shortened to the Getty Research Institute (GRI). The GRI occupies a round, five-level building at the Getty Center that includes an exhibition gallery, a lecture hall, meeting facilities, offices for staff and scholars, and the Research Library.
  - Preliminary Guide to the Collections, Archives of the History of Art. Santa Monica: 1985. (Box 2010.IA.01-15)
  - The J. Paul Getty Trust, Program Review, 1981-1985. Los Angeles: 1985. (Box 2010.IA.01-16)
  - The J. Paul Getty Trust, Fine Arts Center. 1986. (Box 2010.IA.01-16)
  - The J. Paul Getty Trust, Report 1986-1988. Los Angeles: 1988. (Box 2010.IA.01-16)
  - Wagner, Otto. Modern Architecture: A Guidebook for His Students to this Field of Art. Santa Monica: 1988., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04-13)
  - Freedberg, David, and Jan de Vries, eds. Art in History: History in Art: Studies in Seventeenth-Century Dutch Culture. Santa Monica: 1991. (Box 2012.IA.01-08)
    Series: Issues and Debates.
  - New Geographies of Performance: Cultural Representation and the Intercultural Exchange on the Edge of the 21st Century, Summary Report. Los Angeles: 1991. (Box 2010.IA.01-15)
  - Corboz, André. Looking for a City in America: Down These Mean Streets a Man Must Go--: an essay by André Corboz. Santa Monica: 1992. (Box 2012.IA.01-08)
  - Gaehtgens, Thomas W., Heinz Ickstadt, eds. American Icons: Transatlantic Perspectives on Eighteenth- and Nineteenth-Century American Art. Santa Monica: 1992. (Box 2012.IA.01-08)
    Series: Issues & Debates.
  - Hübsch, Heinrich, Rudolf Wiegmann, Carl Albert Rosenthal, Johann Heinrich Wolff, and Carl Gottlieb Wilhelm Bötticher. In What Style Should we Build?: The German Debate on Architectural Style. Translated by Wolfgang Herrmann. Santa Monica: 1992. (Box 2012.IA.01-18)
    Series: Texts and Documents.
  - Labrot, Gerard. Italian Inventories 1: Collections of Paintings in Naples 1600-1780. New York: 1992. (Box 2012.IA.01-18)
    Series: Documents for the History of Collecting
  - Le Camus de Mézières, Nicolas. The Genius of Architecture, or, The Analogy of That Art with Our Sensations. Santa Monica: 1992. (Box 2012.IA.01-11)
  - Perrault, Claude. Ordonnance For the Five Kinds of Columns After the Method of the Ancients. Edited by Harry F. Mallgrave. Santa Monica: 1993. (Box 2012.IA.01-27)
  - Mallgrave, Harry Francis, ed. Otto Wagner: Reflections on the Rainment of Modernity. Santa Monica: 1993. (Box 2012.IA.01-28)
  - Britt, David, trans. Friedrich Gilly: Essays on Architecture 1796 - 1799. Santa Monica: 1994. (Box 2012.IA.01-11)
  - Britt, David, trans. Friedrich Gilly: Essays on Architecture 1796 - 1799. Santa Monica: 1994. (Box 2012.IA.01-28)
  - The Information Infrastructure: Reaching Society's Goals: Report of the Information Infrastructure Task Force Committee on Applications and Technology. Gaithersburg, MD: 1994. (Box 2010.IA.01-15)
  - The J. Paul Getty Trust Report 1993-1994. 1994. (Box 2010.IA.01-16)
  - Mallgrave, Harry Francis, and Eleftherios Ikonomou, trans.Empathy, Form and Space: Problems in German Aesthetics, 1873-1893. Santa Monica: 1994. (Box 2012.IA.01-28)
  - Muthesius, Hermann. Style-Architecture and Building-Art: Transformation of Architecture in the Nineteenth Century and its Present Condition. Translated by Stanford Anderson. Santa Monica: 1994. (Box 2012.IA.01-28)
  - Petersen, Toni, dir. Art and Architecture Thesaurus, Second Edition. Volume 1-5. New York: 1994. (Box 2005.IA.16-01)
  - Union List of Artist Names.Volume 1-4. New York: 1994. (Box 2005.IA.16-02)
  - The Getty Around the Globe, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 9-10, 1995. 1995. (Box 2010.IA.01-15)
  - The Getty in Los Angeles, A Report to the Board of Trustees of the J. Paul Getty Museum, June 8, 1995. 1995. (Box 2010.IA.01-16)
  - Giedion, Sigfried. Building in France: Building in Iron: Building in Ferro-Concrete. Santa Monica: 1995. (Box 2012.IA.01-08)
  - Grant, Alice, Josephine Nieuwenhuis and Toni Petersen, eds.International Guidelines for Museum Object Information: The CIDOC Information Categories: June 1995. Paris: 1995. (Box 2010.IA.01-16)
  - Behne, Adolf. The Modern Functional Building. Santa Monica: 1996. (Box 2012.IA.01-09)
  - Berlage, Hendrik Petrus. Thoughts on Style, 1886-1909. Translated by Iain Boyd White and Wim de Wit. Santa Monica: 1996. (Box 2012.IA.01-28)
  - The Getty, 1995-1996. Los Angeles: 1996. (Box 2010.IA.01-16)
  - Opening Year at the Getty Center, Meeting of the Board of Trustees of the J. Paul Getty Trust, September 11-12, 1996. 1996. (Box 2010.IA.01-15)
  - Safarik, Eduard A. The Colonna Italian Inventories: Collections of Paintings: Inventories 1611-1795. New Providence: 1996. (Box 2012.IA.01-18)
  - Burke, Marcus B., and Peter Cherry. Collections of Paintings in Madrid 1601-1755, Part 1. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-19)
    Series: Documents for the history of collecting. Spanish inventories 1.
  - Burke, Marcus B., and Peter Cherry. Collections of Paintings in Madrid 1601-1755, Part 2. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-19)
  - Kostman, Lynne, ed. Russian Modernism: The Collections of the Getty Research Institute for the History of Art and Humanities. Santa Monica: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-28)
    Series: Bibliographies and Dossiers.
  - Roth, Michael S., Claire Lyons, Charles Merewether. Irresistible Decay: Ruins Reclaimed. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-09)
    Series: Bibliographies & Dossiers.
  - Salatino, Kevin. Incendiary Art: The Representation of Fireworks in Early Modern Europe. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-09)
  - Visual Resources: An International Journal of Documentation, Volume XIII, Number 1. Netherlands: 1997. (Box 2010.IA.01-14)
  - Ciammitti, Luisa, Steven F. Ostrow, and Salvatore Settis, eds. Dosso's Fate: Painting and Court Culture in Renaissance Italy. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-09)
  - Mapping Local Knowledge, A Project of the Getty Research Institute for the History of Art and the Humanities. 1998. (Box 2010.IA.01-15)
  - Morselli, Raffaella. Italian Inventories 3: Collezioni e Quadrerie nella Bologna del Seicento: Inventari 1640-1707. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-19)
    Series: Documents for the History of Collecting. Italian Inventories 3.
  - Post, Robert C., ed. Censorship and Silencing: Practices of Cultural Regulation. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-18)
    Series: Issues and debates.
  - The Report of the J. Paul Getty Trust 97-98. 1998. (Box 2010.IA.01-15)
  - Senior Research Grants: Ten-Year Report, 1988-1998: Collaborative Projects. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2010.IA.01-16)
  - World Culture Report 1998, Culture, Creativity and Markets. Unesco Publishing, Paris: 1998. (Box 2010.IA.01-16)
  - America's Museums. American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Cambridge, MA: 1999. (Box 2010.IA.01-15)
  - BHA: Bibliography of the History of Art, Volume 9/1 and 9/2. Santa Monica: 1999. (Box 2010.IA.01-11)
  - BHA: Bibliography of the History of Art, Volume 9/3 and 9/4. Santa Monica: 1999. (Box 2010.IA.01-11)
  - BHA: Bibliography of the History of Art, Volume 9, Cumulative Index, English. Santa Monica: 1999. (Box 2010.IA.01-11)
  - BHA: Bibliography of the History of Art, Volume 9, Index Cumulatif, Francais. Santa Monica: 1999. (Box 2010.IA.01-11)
  - BHA: Bibliography of the History of Art, List of Journals Indexed, 1999. (Box 2010.IA.01-11)
  - Hess, Catherine. Maiolica in the Making: The Gentili/Barnabel Archive. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-28)
    Condition: Front cover (softcover book) has been vertically creased, but is still in usable condition.
  - The J. Paul Getty Trust 98-99. 1999. (Box 2010.IA.01-15)
  - Kostka, Alexandre, and Irving Wohlfarth, eds. Nietzsche and "An Architecture of Our Minds". Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-28)
  - Riegl, Alois. The Group Portraiture of Holland. Translated by Evelyn M. Kain and David Britt. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-28)
  - Satō, Dōshin. Modern Japanese Art and the Meiji State: The Politics of Beauty. Translated by Hiroshi Nara. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2013.IA.01-1)
  - Scott, Cynthia. Museums, Libraries, and Archives: Summer Institute for Knowledge Sharing. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2010.IA.01-15)
  - Thornes, Robin. Introduction to Object ID: Guidelines for Making Records that Describe Art, Antiques, and Antiquities. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 15)
  - Warburg, Aby. The Renewal of Pagan Antiquity: Contributions to the Cultural History or the European Renaissance. Translated by David Britt. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-29)
  - Zorich, Diane M. Introduction to Managing Digital Assets. Los Angeles: 1999., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 15)
  - Behrendt, Walter Curt. The Victory of the New Building Style. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-11)
  - Durand, Jean-Nicholas-Louis. Précis of the Lectures on Architecture. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-11)
  - Paul, Carole. Making a Prince's Museum: Drawings for the Late-Eighteenth-Century Redecoration of the Villa Borghese. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-18)
  - Strategic Planning Framework. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2010.IA.01-15)
  - Teige, Karel. Modern Architecture in Czechoslovakia and Other Writings. Translated by Irena Žantovská Murray and David Britt. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-28)
  - Biesboer, Pieter. Collections of Paintings in Haarlem 1572-1745. Edited by Carol Togneri. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-20)
    Series: Documents for the History of Collecting. Netherlandish inventories; 1.
  - The New York International Festival of the Arts 1986-2001, 15 Years of Arts Advocacy: Where Will it Take Us? 2001. (Box 2010.IA.01-15)
  - Roth, Michael S., and Charles G. Salas, eds. Disturbing Remains: Memory, History, and Crisis in the Twentieth Century. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-09)
  - Salas, Charles G., and Michael S. Roth, eds. Looking for Los Angeles: Architecture, Film, Photography, and the Urban Landscape. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-29)
    Series: Lectures and Debates.
  - Stafford, Barbara Maria, and Frances Terpak. Devices of Wonder: From the World in a Box to Images on a Screen. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-09)
  - Baca, Murtha, ed. Introduction to Art Image Access: Issues, Tools, Standards, Strategies. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-29)
  - Barkan, Elazar, and Ronald Bush, eds. Claiming the Stones - Naming the Bones: Cultural Property and the Negotiation of National and Ethnic Identity. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-19)
  - Carus, Carl Gustav. Nine Letters on Landscape Painting: Written in the Years 1815-1824: With a Letter from Goethe by Way of Introduction. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-09)
    Series: Texts & Documents.
  - Lyons, Claire L. and John K. Papadopoulos. The Archaeology of Colonialism. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-18)
  - Piranesi, Giovanni Battista. Observations on the Letter of Monsieur Mariette: with Opinions on Architecture, and a Preface to a New Treatise on the Introduction and Progress of the Fine Arts in Europe in Ancient Times. Translated by Caroline Beamish and David Britt. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-28)
  - Armstrong, Carol. Odd Man Out: Readings of the Work and Reputation of Edgar Degas. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-09)
  - Besser, Howard. Introduction to Imaging, Revised Edition. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-29)
  - Clayson, Hollis. Painted Love: Prostitution in French Art of the Impressionist Era. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-29)
  - Gordon, Alden R. The Houses and Collections of the Marquis de Marigny. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-09)
    Series: Documents from the History of Collecting. French inventories; 1.
  - Meyer, Richard, ed. Representing the Passions: Histories, Bodies, Visions. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-09)
  - Perloff, Nancy, and Brian Reed, eds. Situating El Lissitzky: Vitebsk, Berlin, Moscow. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-29)
  - Band, Arnold J., ed. Had Gadya: The Only Kid: Facsimile of El Lissitzky's Edition of 1919. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-09)
  - Beer, Olivier. Lucien Hervé: Building Images. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-10)
  - Le Roy, Julien-David. The Ruins of the Most Beautiful Monuments of Greece. Translated by David Britt. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-29)
  - Semper, Gottfried. Style: Style in the Technical and Tectonic Arts; or, Practical Aesthetics. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-10)
  - Burckhardt, Jacob. Italian Renaissance Painting According to Genres. Translated by David Britt and Caroline Beamish. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 2012.IA.01-29)
  - Phillips, Glenn, and Thomas Crow, eds.Seeing Rothko. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-19)
  - Hyde, Melissa, and Mark Ledbury, eds. Rethinking Boucher. Los Angele: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-01)
  - Hyde, Melissa, Making up the Rococo. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 1987.IA.04-19)
  - Painter, Karen, and Thomas Crow, eds. Late Thoughts: Reflections on Artists and Composers at Work. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-01)
  - Research Library Council, Founding Meeting, Thursday, 23 March, 2006. 2006. (Box 2010.IA.01-15)
  - Winckelmann, Johann Joachim. History of the Art of Antiquity. Translated by Harry Francis Mallgrave. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 1987.IA.04-19)
  - L.A. Art Online: Learning from the Getty's Electronic Cataloguing Initiative. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2010.IA.01-15)
  - L.A. Art Online: Learning from the Getty's Electronic Cataloguing Initiative. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2008.IA.01-01)
  - Le Corbusier. Toward an Architecture. Translated by John Goodman. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2012.IA.01-29)
  - Loh, Maria H. Titian Remade: Repetition and the Transformation of Early Modern Italian Art. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2012.IA.01-10)
  - Merewether, Charles and Rika Iezumi Hiro. Art, Anti-Art, Non-Art: Experimentations in the Public Sphere in Postwar Japan, 1950-1970: Catalog of an Exhibition Held at the Getty Research Institute, Mar. 6-June 3, 2007. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-02)
  - Research Library Council, Second Annual Meeting, Thursday, 5 April, 2007. 2007. (Box 2010.IA.01-15)
  - Salas, Charles G., ed. The Life & The Work: Art and Biography. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2012.IA.01-18)
  - Baca, Murtha, ed. Introduction to Metadata. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-01)
  - Cummins, Thomas B. F., and Barbara Anderson, eds. The Getty Murúa: Essays on the Making of Martin de Murúa's "Historia General del Piru," J. Paul Getty Museum Ms. Ludwig XIII 16. Los Angeles: 2008., (2 copies) (Box 2009.IA.01-05)
  - De Murúa, Martin. Historia General del Piru: Facsimile of J. Paul Getty Museum Ms. Ludwig XIII 16. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2009.IA.01-05)
  - Kaprow, Allan. Art as Life. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-01)
  - Lichtenstein, Jacqueline. The Blind Spot: an Essay on the Relations Between Painting and Sculpture in the Modern Age. Translated by Chris Miller. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2012.IA.01-19)
  - Panzanelli, Roberta, trans. Ephemeral Bodies: Wax Sculpture and the Human Figure. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2012.IA.01-11)
  - Phillips, Glenn, ed. California Video: Artists and Histories. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-02)
  - Esterman, Daniel, ed.Meyer Schapiro Abroad: Letters to Lillian and Travel Notebooks. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2008.IA.01-02)
  - Gaehtgens, Thomas W., ed. Getty Research Journal, Number 1 - 2009. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2012.IA.01-10)
  - Naginski, Erika. Sculpture and Enlightenment. Los Angeles: 2009., (2 copies) (Box 2009.IA.01-03)
  - Tronzo, William, ed.The Fragment: An Incomplete History. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2008.IA.01-02)
  - Dubin, Nina L. Futures & Ruins: Eighteenth-Century Paris and The Art of Hubert Robert. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-04)
  - Gaehtgens, Thomas W., ed. Getty Research Journal, Number 2 - 2010. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2012.IA.01-10)
  - Harpring, Patricia. Introduction to Controlled Vocabularies: Terminology for Art, Architecture, and other Cultural Works. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2012.IA.01-29)
  - Hunt, Lynn, Margaret Jacob, Wijnand Mijnhardt, eds.Bernard Picart and the First Global Vision of Religion. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-04)
  - Marchesano, Louis and Michel, Christian. Printing the Grand Manner: Charles le Brun and Monumental Prints in the Age of Louis XIV. Los Angeles: 2010., (copy 1 of 2) (Box 2010.IA.01-17)
  - Marchesano, Louis and Michel, Christian. Printing the Grand Manner: Charles le Brun and Monumental Prints in the Age of Louis XIV. Los Angeles: 2010., (copy 2 of 2) (Box 2011.IA.01-05)
  - Mertins, Detlef, and Michael W. Jennings, eds.G: An Avant-Garde Journal of Art, Architecture, Design, and Film, 1923-1926. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-04)